<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on CapitalMu</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on CapitalMu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Technology Assistance</title>
      <link>/services/tech-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/tech-services/</guid>
      <description>We provide a wide range of blockchain related technology services, and we are also willing to received customized services for our clients.
Delegate Agency We help other delegates maintain their nodes:
[1] 24/7 technical support[2] Solid techincal team to ensure the operation[3] Real-time report including various indicators for Node[4] 99.9% server up time with server failover, won&amp;rsquo;t miss any block[5] Close collaboration with IoTeX team, kept up to date with latest development and upgrades</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OTC Trading</title>
      <link>/services/otc-trading/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/otc-trading/</guid>
      <description>We provide Block Trade for IOTX (OTC market)  most cost efficient solutions transparent for trading details customized services based on your needs  IOTX OTC Trading Guideline &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash; Faster + Easier   Drop an email to admin@capitalmu.com: tell us your BUY/SELL amount and expected price Exchange address via social media: Telegram/Wechat/WhatsApp/etc. Small amount trial transaction Left balance transaction Send confirmation email for this OTC transaction to you  Done!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoTeX Delegate</title>
      <link>/services/iotex-delegate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/iotex-delegate/</guid>
      <description>CapitalMu is IoTeX&amp;rsquo;s strategic partner and academic collaborator, our university-based research and devlopment team is committed to contribute to IoTeX community diversity and ecosystem maturity.
Who are we? We are a research team based in the National University of Singapore, consists of professor, financial industry practitioner, lecturer, researcher, and developers.
Our main research and development interests are:
 Quantitative Finance: Market Sentiment Analysis, Machine learning and AI, Algorithmic trading strategies, derivative products, on both traditional financial market and cryptocurrency Blockchain Technology and Its Applications: Token economics, Blockchain applications in financial industry and emerging markets, Blockchain technology for a smart nation, where IoT plays an extremely critical role.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
